Patient: So, what does it mean, Doctor?
Doctor: Well, first the party.
A party is a group of people.
This means that you’re going to meet a lot of people.
I think you’re going to be very busy.
Patient: At work?
Doctor: Yes, at work… you work in an office, I think?
Patient: Yes, that’s right.
Doctor: I think the party means you’re going to have lots of meetings.
Patient: What about the champagne?
Doctor: Let me look at my notes again.
Champagne means a celebration. It’s a symbol of success.
So we have a meeting or meetings and then a celebration.
Maybe, in the future, you’ll have a meeting with your boss, about a possible promotion?
Patient: Well, it’s possible. I hope so…
What about the garden and the flowers? Do they mean anything?
Doctor: Yes. Flowers are a positive symbol.
So, the flowers mean that you are feeling positive about the future.
So perhaps you already knew about this possible promotion?
Patient: No, I didn’t. But it’s true, I am very happy at work and I feel very positive about my future.
That’s not where my problems are. My problems are with my love life.
Does my dream tell you anything about that?
Doctor: Mm, yes it does.
You’re single, aren’t you?
Patient: Yes, well… divorced.
Doctor: Because the violin music tells me you want some romance in your life –
you’re looking for a partner, perhaps?
Patient: Yes, yes, I am. In fact, I met a woman last month.
I really like her…
I think I’m in love with her.
I’m meeting her tonight.
Doctor: In your dream you saw an owl in a tree?
Patient: Yes, an owl… a big owl.
Doctor: The owl represents a wise person.
I think you’ll need to ask this wise person for help.
Maybe this ‘wise person’ is me?
Maybe you need my help?
Patient: Well, yes, what I want to know is, does this woman… love me?